《好漢兩個半》前情提要
Previously on Two and a Half Men...
我死了
I'm dead.
你人在醫院呢
You're in the hospital.
你犯了輕微心臟病
You had a mild heart attack.
我差點死掉  艾倫
I almost died, Alan.
但重要的是你沒有死
But the important thing is you didn't.
除了你們和我媽  我就沒有別人了
Other than you guys and my mom, I got nobody.
至少你還有杰克
At least you got Jake.
我想有個自己的孩子
I want to have a kid of my own.
-你的條件非常好  -謝謝
- You are obviously more than qualified. - Thank you.
我會著手幫你找一只黃金獵犬幼犬
I'd start looking at golden retriever puppies,
因為你根本不可能領養到孩子
'cause there's no way you're getting a baby.
你是單身男性
You're a single guy, and the system
本機構更傾向于已婚夫婦
is really geared towards married couples.
艾倫·哈勃  嫁給我好嗎
Alan Harper, will you marry me?
時至今日
等等  你真的想娶我嗎
Wait. You seriously want to marry me?
是的
Yes.
艾倫·杰羅姆·哈勃
Alan Jerome Harper,
你愿意當我的妻...
would you be my wi...?
丈...
Hus...?
人生伙伴嗎
Life buddy?
我其實有點迷糊
Okay, I'm a little confused.
跟我某次被人妖按摩的那種"迷糊"不一樣
And not like the time I-I got that massage from that lady-boy.
我想要領養一孩子
Look, I want to adopt a kid,
而對我來說  最快的方法就是結婚
and the quickest way for me to do that is to get married.
如果我得隨便挑個人過
And if I'm gonna settle for someone,
還不如跟你過呢
it might as well be you.
我第一任妻子也是這么說的
That's exactly what my first wife said.
我知道這聽起來很瘋狂
Listen, I-I know this sounds crazy,
但你可以幫我這輩子最大的一個忙
but you would be doing me the biggest favor of my life.
沃頓  外面有千千萬萬個女人
Walden, there are literally millions of women
搶破頭都要跟你結婚
who would marry you at the drop of a hat.
但跟她們在一起不會有
Yeah, but I wouldn't be half as happy
跟你在一起時的一半快樂
with any of them as I would be with you.
接著說
Go on.
我對我老婆有十個要求
When-when I think of the ten things I want in a wife,
你能做到其中九個
you have nine of them.
你是我最好的朋友  你值得信任
You're my best friend, you're trustworthy,
你充滿了愛  你很聰明  你永遠不會離開我
you're loving, you're smart, you'll never leave me.
不管結沒結婚  到死都賴著你
Married or not, till death do us part.
你很幽默  你懂我心思
You're funny, you're understanding.
你不在意我有沒有把馬桶座放下
You don't care if I leave the toilet seat up.
其實正合我意
I actually prefer it.
不過有一天晚上  我忘了它沒放下來
Although, the other night, I forgot it was up,
我一個撲通就掉下水
and I had a surprise splash-down.
感覺就像青蛙翻了身
I was like a turtle on its back.
你看  這又是另一個我喜歡的點
Right there. That's another one.
只要你在我身邊
As long as you're around,
我永遠不會是場上最丟人的一個
I will never be the most awkward guy in the room.
所以我沒有滿足
So, what's the one thing
你對你老婆的要求的唯一一點是什么
you want in a wife that I don't have?
懂了  懂了
Oh. Right, right.
那個東西我沒有
I-I do not have one of those.
我有的"這個"都不是很夠數了
I barely have one of these.
所以  我是該怎么幫你呢
I mean, how would this work exactly?
我們就假裝是一對夫妻嗎
I mean, we're gonna pretend to be a couple?
我們不是假裝
We wouldn't pretend.
我們就當一對真的同性已婚夫妻
We're actually going to be a same-sex married couple.
而就跟大多數已婚夫婦一樣  我們不做愛
And like most married couples, we will not have sex.
我生日那天也不做嗎
Not even on my birthday?
抱歉  抱歉  回想起跟前妻的往事了
Sorry, sorry... flashback to the first wife.
所以我可以瘋狂地跟任何女人
So, so, I can have crazy, anonymous sex
隨便做愛嗎
with any woman I want?
不會  你始終還是原來的你
No. You will still be you.
好吧
Oh.
艾倫·哈勃施密特先生
Mr. Alan Harper-Schmidt.
艾倫·施密特醫生
Dr. Alan Schmidt.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我試試哪一種念起來比較好聽
Oh, just trying to see what sounds best.
是的  哈勃施密特先生與先生
Yes, Mr. And Mr. Harper-Schmidt,
歡迎回到四季酒店
welcome back to the Four Seasons.
你們的海景房已經準備妥當
Your ocean front suite is ready.
少說屎[施密特]話了
Okay, cut the Schmidt.
對哦  我還得忍受這件屎事
Oh, yeah, I'd have to put up with that Schmidt.
不過呢  我掌握得住
But you know what? I'm gonna own it.
我才不鳥這些屎事
I don't give a Schmidt.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我意思是好  我嫁給你  你個大笨屎密特
I'm saying, yes, I'll marry you, you big dumb Schmidt.
請告訴我  你褲襠鼓起的是護唇膏
Oh, please tell me that's ChapStick in your pocket.
■
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
好漢兩個半
第十二季  第二集
翻譯：9尺神筆賽太公   萬丈深淵YY貓   貓中之王   大菜
校對：9尺神筆賽太公   萬丈深淵YY貓  總監   YY貓
媽  謝謝你來一趟
Hi, Mom. Thanks for coming over.
啥事這么重要
What is so important
后期：灰灰是菇涼  時間軸：YY貓
我比基尼熱蠟除毛到一半也拉我來
that I had to leave halfway through my bikini wax?
我下面看起來像黑白餅干
I look like a black and white cookie.
你一句話摧毀了我對餅干與陰部的愛
In one fell swoop, there goes cookies and vaginas.
怎么回事
What's going on?
不會又是開批斗會吧
Is this another intervention?
我再說第一百萬次  我沒有酗酒問題
For the millionth time, I do not have a drinking problem.
不是的  伊芙琳  這是慶祝
No, Evelyn. It's-it's a celebration.
如果是這樣
Well, in that case,
我要一杯雙份馬丁尼  別放苦艾酒哦
I'll have a double martini and hold the vermouth.
你好  我是羅賓  沃頓的媽媽
Hello. I'm Robin. I'm Walden's mother.
很高興終于見到你
Oh, how nice to finally meet you.
你有個很棒的兒子  以及很棒的雙峰
You have a wonderful son and amazing breasts.
誰做的
Who did them?
上天做的
God?
他始終還是業界第一
Well, he's still the best.
不過申克曼醫生的手藝也離他不遠了
Although Dr. Schenkman runs a close second.
的確是很棒
They are lovely.
好了  大家可以不要在談論我媽的胸了嗎
Okay, can everyone stop talking about my mom's boobs? God.
我終于知道為何高中時我這么多朋友了
Oh, my God, that's why I had so many friends in high school.
所以有什么大事要宣布
So, what's the big announcement?
其實呢
Uh... Well...
艾倫與我...
Alan and I...
我們要結婚了
We're getting married!
喂  你搞毛  說好了我來宣布
Dude! What the hell! We agreed I was gonna say it.
抱歉抱歉  我太激動了
Sorry, sorry. I'm just so excited.
無意冒犯  但你找不到比艾倫更好的嗎
Uh, no offense, but can't you do better than Alan?
等等  你要娶他嗎
Back up. You are marrying him?
是啊
Yup.
干嘛打我
What was that for?
因為你要娶廢柴
For marrying Zippy.
那你干嘛打我
Hey! Why are you hitting me?!
因為你是廢柴
For being Zippy.
這聽起來不錯啊  除了一個問題
This sounds great, except for one thing.
你們不是基
You guys aren't gay.
不  我們不是基
No, we're not gay.
我們結婚是因為
We are getting married because...
這樣他要領養孩子比較容易
it'll make it easier for him to adopt a child!
干嘛又搶我詞
Aah, come on!
謝謝  波塔
Uh, thank you, Berta.
等等  你想領養個孩子
Hold on. You want a child?
是的
Yes.
我最近一直在思考我的人生
I've been doing a lot of thinking about my life,
我相信孩子能為我的人生
and I believe that having a kid
增添更多意義
would add more meaning to it.
為人父母的確能獲益良多
Parenthood can be very rewarding.
但也不盡然
Some of the time.
所以你們只是假結婚嗎
So, this marriage is just a sham?
我去參加那些同性戀游行
I didn't march in all of those gay rights parades
可不是來讓你們玩弄
so you guys could make a mockery of
我們拼來的公民自由
our hard-won civil liberties.
你去參加那些游行
You marched in those parades
不過是為了喝酒和泡妞
so you could get drunk and pick up chicks.
拼來的妞
Hard-won chicks.
好啦  聽著我們沒有玩弄任何事物
All right, look, we're not making a mockery of anything,
我也明白同性戀伴侶會面臨什么挑戰
and I get the challenges that gay couples face,
但我還知道這世上有很多孩子
but I-I also know that there are a lot of kids out there
在尋找一個好的家庭
that are just looking for a good home,
而我們可以提供一個家啊
and I think we can provide that.
這樣我也有醫保了
And I get health insurance.
你們真該慶幸你們是在加州
You guys are lucky you're in California.
在某些州仍不允許同性戀結婚
In some states, they still don't let gay couples get married
或領養孩子
or adopt kids.
當我在猶他州時
You know, when I was in Utah,
我吐在一名警察身上
I vomited on a police officer,
結果被逮捕了
and I was arrested.
就因為我是同性戀
Simply for being gay.
這信息量太大了
Wow, this is a lot to take in.
我的兒子要結婚要領養孩子  而伴侶是...
My son is going to get married and have a child with...
上帝啊  我到底做錯了什么啊
Oh, God, where... where did I go wrong?
他回來了  我的同性伴侶
Oh, there he is, my same-sex shorty.
我同住不同床的朋友
My friend with no benefits.
我的情郎
My boo.
我有99個問題  而你就是全部的根源
You know, I do have 99 problems, and you're all of them.
這些都是什么
What's all this?
我...
Uh, oh, I'm, uh...
我在做我們婚禮的夢想板
I'm making a dream board for our wedding.
在品趣志也有一個頁面
Uh, there's also a Pinterest page,
或者你可以輸入艾倫和沃頓大喜之日.com
or you can go to: Alan and Walden's big day dot com.
我知道  我收到你發的鏈接了
Yeah, I got the link you sent me.
我很喜歡你電腦合成的那張照片
Uh, I really loved the photoshopped picture
就是我們倆從一棵樹后面探出頭來
of both us peeking around the same tree.
不管怎樣
However, you know,
我們不會辦一個奢華的大型婚禮
we're not doing, like, a big, lavish wedding.
沒事  我懂
Oh, okay, I get it.
在度假地辦個小型婚禮也行
You know, small destination wedding.
咱倆在海灘
Just the two of us, the beach,
脖子上戴著花環
wearing leis around our necks,
身著情侶亞麻襯衫  沙子在親吻我們的腳趾
matching linen shirts, sand tickling our toes.
海鷗在我們頭上盤旋
Seagulls flying overhead.
你怎么會瞎想到這種畫面呢
And where do you see this happening?
顯然  我們有夏威夷和卡波海灘可供選擇
Well, obviously, there's Hawaii and Cabo.
隨便哪個我都沒意見
I'd be happy with either one of those.
但我聽說這個季節的希臘非常美
Um, but I hear that Greece is fabulous this time of year.
順便說一句  米科諾斯對同性伴侶可是非常友好喲
And just FYI, Mykonos is very friendly to same-sex couples.
好吧
Opa!
不好吧
Nopa!
我們會在法院結婚
We're getting married in the courthouse.
請告訴我"法院"是地中海伊比沙島的一間時髦酒吧
Please tell me the "courthouse" is a chic bar in Ibiza.
不  就在連鎖潤滑油公司
No, it's a rundown courthouse
轉角處的一間破舊的法院
around the corner from the Jiffy Lube.
花50塊錢
We'll pay 50 bucks,
簽一些文件
we'll do some paperwork,
如果你沒意見  我們可以去外面的快餐車
and if you're good, we'll go outside to the food truck,
給你買個希臘皮塔三明治
and I'll buy you a gyro.
好吧
Opa!
好吧  我懂了
Okay. I see.
怎么了
What's wrong?
沒事
Nothing.
說吧
Talk to me.
真沒事
No, it's fine.
我只是想盡力確保
You know, I just wanted to make sure
整件事是特別的  無論是對我們而言
this whole thing was special for us,
還是對你而言  但其實也沒什么大不了的
for you, but, you know, it's no big deal.
我相信我們仍能讓它變得特別
I'm sure we can still make it special.
或許就讓珍妮拿手機  幫我們拍幾張照片吧
Maybe, uh... maybe Jenny can take some pictures on her iPhone.
艾倫  別這樣
Alan, come on.
別碰我
Don't touch me.
這事的重點不是我們
Look, this isn't about us.
而是我們要領養一個孩子
It's about bringing a kid into our lives.
這只是簡單的商業交易
It's a simple business transaction,
就像交電費  或請客吃飯  或...
like paying an electric bill, or buying dinner, or...
寫支票交房租
writing a rent check.
麻煩在我說到你有做過的事情時喊停
Stop me when I land on something you've actually done.
人家剛才超興奮的
I just got excited
因為我從未擁有過夢想中的婚禮
because I've never had the wedding I always dreamed of.
是啊  那些小少男的白日夢婚禮
Right, the wedding that every little boy dreams of.
我們還是要給對方買戒指的
You know, we still need to get each other rings.
隨便在網上買倆就行
We can just get something online.
或者我們可以去比佛利山莊  吃個早午餐
Or we could go into Beverly Hills and have brunch,
然后一起去買戒指
and go ring shopping together.
真的嗎
Really?
當然
Sure.
因為我的確對戒指有些想法
Because I do have ideas.
波塔  咱們家有"白"蘿卜嗎
Hey, Berta, do we have any carrots?
慢著  我有一只14克拉的"白"金戒指
Oh, wait. I've got 14 karats of white gold
請看這里
right here.
你會是一個漂亮的新娘  廢柴
You'll make a beautiful bride, Zippy.
我未來寶寶的爸爸來了
Hey, there's my future baby daddy!
如果要我聽這種肉麻對話  那我要大漲薪水
If I got to listen to this, I got to be a lot higher.
我這有些文件需要你簽
Hey, uh, I got some paperwork for you to sign.
我也有些文件需要你簽
Oh, uh, and I've got some paperwork for you to sign.
人們說得沒錯  已婚夫婦想法會變得一致
Guess it's true. Married couples do start to think alike.
或許不久后  我們長相也會一致
Maybe soon, we'll start to look alike,
他滿懷希望地說
he said hopefully.
這是我們結婚證的申請書
It's the application form for our marriage license.
-瞧瞧你  -是啊
- Oh, look at you. - Yeah.
我猜某人會拿這筆錢
I guess somebody's gonna get that money
去做一直想做的手部和足部護理
for that Mani-pedi he wants after all.
是你寵壞人家啦
Ah, you spoil me.
不是啦  我只是努力當個生意好伙伴
No, I'm just trying to be a good business partner.
你棒  我棒  雙棒合璧
The Johnson to your Johnson.
等等  這話聽起來怎么這么別扭
Wait, that-that didn't come out right.
那你想讓我簽什么
So, uh... so what do you need me to sign?
這個
Uh, just this.
那是什么
Oh. What's that?
只是一份簡單的散伙服務協議
Oh, it's a simple dissolution of services agreement.
比如像婚前協議書嗎
Oh, you-you mean, like a... like a prenup?
對  這沒什么大不了的
Yup. So, it's not a big deal.
快簽吧  他滿懷希望地說
Just go ahead and sign it, he said hopefully.
我們為什么要簽婚前協議
Why do we need a prenup?
果不其然
And here we go.
一對伴侶結婚時
When couples get married,
財產變得很復雜
finances become complicated,
這樣就能簡化了
and this just simplifies it.
是嗎
Oh, does it?
因為現在的狀況倒是挺簡單的
'Cause it seems like it's pretty simple right now.
你不信任我
You don't trust me.
不是這樣的
Okay, that's not true at all.
是嗎
Isn't it?
你就是這么看待我的
I mean, is this what you really think of me?
我就是一個拜金男嗎
That I'm some kind of gold digger?
好吧是的  我在這里免費住了四年
Okay, yes, I have lived here four years rent-free.
你干嘛非得把這事兒搞這么復雜
Look, why do you have to make this difficult?
你干嘛非得把所有事搞這么復雜
You know, why do you make everything so difficult?
比如昨天吃早午餐的時候  你把香檳退了
It's like yesterday at brunch, when you sent back the champagne
因為酒的泡沫嘗起來沒有"滿口星星"的感覺
because the bubbles didn't taste like mouthful of stars?
如果泡沫在嘴里不爆開  還有什么意思
If it doesn't explode in your mouth, what's the point?
你對服務生也這么說的  聽起來就很黃
You said that to the waiter, too, and it was troubling then!
我只是想保護我的財產
Look, I'm just trying to protect my assets.
是嗎  那我也應該保護我的財產
Oh-oh, yeah? Well, then maybe I should protect my assets.
別擔心
You know, don't worry,
我保證你的《熱舞》錄像帶拷貝
I'm pretty sure that your VHS copy of Dirty Dancing
和你的《捉鬼敢死隊》卡牌全集非常安全
and your complete collection of Ghostbusters trading cards are safe.
我喜歡收集80年代的電影物品
I am a collector of '80s movie memorabilia.
嘲笑別人的興趣可不會招人喜歡
And hobby mocking is not an attractive color on you.
興趣嘲笑者
Hobby mocker.
我還有一樣你得不到的財產
I also have one other asset that you cannot have,
我的尊嚴
my dignity.
-你的尊嚴  -是
- Your dignity?! - Mm-hmm.
-你的尊嚴  -是的
- Your dignity...? - Yes.
真的嗎  因為我肯定就是因為你
Really? 'Cause I'm pretty sure that the security guard
超市的保安才不得不把
at the shopping mall had to remove the bench
《維多利亞的秘密》店外的板凳給搬走
from outside of Victoria's Secret because of you!
商場"只看不買"者
Mall flogger!
我告訴你  我現在開始有很多疑慮了哦
I got to tell you, I'm having a lot of second thoughts right now.
是嗎  你以為向一個47歲的男人求婚
Really? Because this is exactly where I want to be in my life,
是我這一生夢寐以求的事情嗎
begging a 47-year-old man to marry me.
快點簽了婚前協議
Now sign the prenup!
我同意和你結婚  不過這并不代表
I agreed to marry you, but that doesn't mean you get
你把什么東西塞進我嘴里
to shove whatever you want down my throat
我就得吞下去
and expect me to swallow it!
你  你聽聽
Do-do you... do you even hear
你說的話不惡心嗎
the words that you are saying?!
那這些話如何  婚禮取消
How about these words? The wedding's off!
連艾倫·哈勃都不愿意跟我結婚
I can't even get Alan Harper to marry me.
小子  你最好有要事
Boy, this better be important.
我兩天前才見了你
I just saw you two days ago.
沃頓和我分手了  婚禮也取消了
Walden and I broke up. The-the wedding is off.
艾倫
Oh, Alan.
你本來手握鉆石王老五
You had a rich husband on the hook
你卻讓他溜走了
and you couldn't reel him in.
發生了什么事
What happened?
他讓我簽婚前協議  我拒絕了
Well, he asked me to sign a prenup and I refused.
你當然得拒絕
Well, of course you refused.
我付錢給人養你長大  可不能養個傻子
The woman I paid to raise you did not raise a fool.
媽媽  我不想要他的錢
Mom, I don't want his money.
再說這種蠢話試試
Never say that again.
這是新的戒指嗎
Is that a new ring?
觸感像卡地亞的
Feels like Cartier.
是的  你知道是誰給我的嗎
Yes, it is. And you know who gave it to me?
我的富老公
My rich husband.
馬蒂和我結婚的時候
When Marty and I married,
我唯一愿意簽署的協議是
the only thing I was willing to sign
"拒絕心肺復蘇術"的協議
was his do not resuscitate order.
沃頓說我們的婚姻只是商業交易
Walden says this wedding is just a-a business transaction.
有多少商業交易
H-How many business transactions end
落得個好結果
with the release of grand monarch butterflies?
親愛的  不要感情用事
Darling, it is just business.
他利用你  得到他想要的
He's using you to get what he wants,
你也應該利用他  得到你想要的
and you should be using him to get what you want:
經濟保障
financial security.
我這么做不是為了經濟保障
I'm not doing it for financial security.
沃頓很想要一個孩子
Walden genuinely wants a child,
正如我想要杰克  正如你想要
the same way that I wanted Jake and-and you wanted...
查理
Charlie.
我以為同居4年
I just thought that after four years together
他應該在錢上面對我很信任
that he would trust me when it comes to money.
親愛的  相識47年  我還是不信任你
Oh, darling, after 47 years, I don't trust you.
或許  婚前協議是合理的
aybe, uh, a-a prenup is justified.
或許我只是一個海綿
Maybe I am just a sponge.
一只寄生蟲
A-a-a parasite.
他一直容忍我  因為他是我最好的朋友
And-and he tolerates me because he's my best friend.
而我卻讓他失望了
And I've let him down,
我只想讓他開心
and all I want to do is make him happy.
最好的朋友  開心
Best friend. Happy.
我不知道你是從哪里學來的
I just have no idea where you got
這些婚姻歪理
these warped views on marriage.
他不肯簽婚前協議
He wouldn't sign a prenup?
對啊  他很不開心還大發脾氣
No, he got all upset and he threw a hissy fit.
你不信任我  婚禮取消
You don't trust me. The wedding's off.
我要一個人去伊比沙島[地中海西岸]
I'm going to Ibiza by myself?
面對現實吧  他配不上你
Let's face it, the man is simply not your equal.
如果你倆同在一架飛機上
If the two of you were on a plane that crashed
飛機撞毀之后  艾倫肯定會第一個被吃掉
in the mountains, Alan would be the first person eaten.
換句話說
On the other hand,
你帥氣  成功  聰明
you're handsome, successful, smart.
你肯定是最后一個被吃掉的
You would be eaten last.
你說我會最后一個被吃掉  因為你是我媽媽
You're just saying I'd be eaten last 'cause you're my mom.
聽我說  我知道你是認真對待孩子的事情
Well, listen, I know you're serious about this child thing,
所以我告訴了公司的一個可愛的實習生
so I mentioned your situation to a very cute intern at work.
不是吧
You didn't.
潔西卡非常能接受這種交易
Oh, Jessica's very amenable to striking a business deal.
還有
Plus,
她已經拜訪了隆乳圣手申克曼醫生
she's already visited Dr. Schenkman,
你肯定懂我的意思吧
if you know what I mean.
媽媽  我就是不想這樣
Mom, that's exactly what I don't want.
我都不認識這個...
I don't even know this Jess...
我勒個申克曼
Holy Schenkman.
我...
Look, I-I w...
不  她會第一個被"吃"掉
No, she'd be eaten first.
我需要一個我能信任的人
Look, no, I want someone that I can trust.
所以我才優先選擇了艾倫
That's why I picked Alan in the first place.
你怎么可能信任他
How can you possibly trust him?
他偷你車里的油
He siphons gas out of your car.
其實我從沒當場抓住過他
Technically, I never caught him.
我猜是他干的
I just assumed that he did it
因為花園的橡膠軟管有汽油的味道
'cause the garden hose smelled like gas
有一次  他在蠟燭旁邊打嗝
and one time he burped near a candle
把沙發都燒起來了
and it lit the couch on fire.
我都不理解一開始
I don't know why you ever
你為什么會讓艾倫住進來
let Alan live with you in the first place.
首先  他救過我的命
Uh, for starters, he saved my life.
其次  他一直陪在我身邊
And... he's been there for me,
每次當我需要他時  他都在
every time that I needed him
連不需要的時候  他都在
and even times when I didn't.
最重要的是...
The bottom line is...
他是我最好的朋友
he's my best friend.
潔西卡也能成為你最好的朋友
Jessica could be your best friend.
我不會和潔西卡約會的
I'm not going out with Jessica.
好  我懂了
Fine. I get it.
還有另一位實習生  你也許會更喜歡
I do have another intern that you might like better.
男孩叫德里克  愛好普拉提
His name is Derek. He does Pilates...
媽  我不是同性戀
Mom, I'm not gay!
我只是想和男人結婚
I-I just want to marry a man.
怎么就這么難理解了呢
Why is that so difficult to understand?
-我說  -之前...
- Listen... - About earlier...
那...是我的錯
Uh, that-that's, that's my fault.
我完全理解為什么要我簽婚前協議
I-I totally get why I need to sign a prenup.
站在高速入口前的假人
I mean, there's guys standing at freeway onramps
賺的都比我多
that make more money than I do.
你不用簽了
You know what, you don't need to sign it.
盡管我母親的反對
Despite my mother's objections
盡管有違我所有的從...
and despite everything I've learned from...
兩季《球星太太團》里學到的知識
two seasons of Basketball Wives,
我完全信任你
I trust you completely.
真貼心  但...
That's nice, but, uh,
我已經簽好寄給你的律師了
I already signed it and sent it to your attorney.
真的嗎
Really?
謝謝你  我欠你一個人情
Thank you. I-I owe you.
你什么都不欠我
You owe me nothing.
除了買信封的兩美元
I mean, other than two dollars for the envelope
和一塊七毛五的郵票錢
and $1.75 for postage.
汽油錢不用我出嗎
Nothing for gas?
不用  我自己加回來了
No, I just filled up.
你還愿意當我丈夫嗎
Will you still be my husband?
你知道我對你欲罷不能
You know I can't quit you.
我知道這并不是
Listen, I-I know this isn't the wedding
你的夢中婚禮
that you've always dreamed of,
但我在婚禮給你準備了驚喜
but I-I got a little surprise for you for the ceremony.
難道是王薇薇開始做燕尾服了嗎
Tell me Vera Wang started making tuxes.
比那更棒
Even better.
* 當一個男人愛上了一個男人 *
* When a man loves another man *
歌壇巨星邁克爾·波頓  原曲為《當男人愛上女人》
* 對他來說什么都不重要了 *
* Can't keep his mind on nothing else *
我  的  天
Oh... my... God.
簡直就像在夢里一般
It's like you live inside my dreams.
老婆好  才是真的好
Happy wife, happy life.
同志們  我們能速戰速決嗎
Uh, fellas, can we get this going?
后面有一大群同性戀情侶還等著
There's a lot of gay couples here who'd like to get married
趕在最高法院改主意之前結婚呢
before the Supreme Court changes its mind.
還有  這地方到處都是條子
Plus, this place is crawling with cops,
我包里還藏著六到十二個月的"罪行"
and I've got six months to a year hidden in my purse.
* 當一個男人愛上了一個男人 *
* When a man loves another man *
別唱了  波頓
Kill it, Bolton.
好啊  邁克爾
Hello, Michael.
我有根電動棒是以你命名哦
You know, I have a vibrator named after you.
受寵若驚
Well, that's very flattering.
用我幫你簽名嗎
Would you like me to sign it?
我有根特殊的"大筆"
I have a special pen.
真巧
What a coincidence.
我有個下流的壞習慣
I have a bit of a nasty habit
喜歡把"筆尖"含在嘴里
of putting the tips of pens into my mouth.
我們在此見證沃頓·施密特
We're here to join Walden Schmidt
和艾倫·哈勃的合法婚姻
and Alan Harper in legal marriage.
有自己的婚誓要宣讀嗎
Have you two written your own vows?
沒有  標準的就行
No, the, uh, standard... the standard
"不論富有還是貧窮"還挺貼切的
"Or richer, for poorer" actually fits us quite well.
其實
Actually,
我自己寫了點東西
I've written a little something down.
什么  你不是吧
What? You didn't.
我想給你驚喜嘛
I wanted to surprise you.
誓言加波頓
Vows and Bolton?
-當一個男人...  -那不是喊你唱歌  波頓
- When a man... -Not the cue, Bolton.
今天
Today,
我要跟我最好的朋友結婚
I'm marrying my best friend.
不許哭
Do not cry.
堅持住  艾倫
Keep it together, Alan.
在過去的四年中  發生了很多事
In the last four years, I've been through a lot.
生活有起有落
Uh, there's been good times and bad times.
但由始至終  你都在我身邊
But through it all, you were there.
我無法想象沒有你的未來
And I can't imagine a future without you.
其實我想告訴你的是...
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
我愛你
I love you.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
這是我參加過最基情的婚禮
This is the gayest wedding I've ever been to.
講得太好了...我屁股上是誰的手
I think it's beaut... Wh-Whose hand is on my ass?
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Sorry. - Sorry.
沃頓
Walden,
你是否愿意接受艾倫成為你的合法丈夫
do you take Alan to be your lawfully wedded husband?
我愿意
I do.
艾倫  你是否愿意接受沃頓成為你的...
And, Alan, do you take Walden to be your...
誰敢攔我試試
Try and stop me.
我宣布你們成為合法伴侶
I now pronounce you married.
你們可以接吻了
You may kiss.
對
Oh. Oh, yeah.
接吻  好的
Um, kiss. Right.
管他呢
Aw, what the hell.
* 當一個男人愛上了一個男人 *
* When a man loves another man... *
早安
Morning.
我的老伴兒來了
Hey. There's the old balls and chain.
你的新婚之夜如何
How was your wedding night?
和第一次結婚一樣
Much like my first one.
我自擼到天明
I spent it masturbating alone.
你是我唯一見過的結婚禮物
You're the only guy I know
要求收乳液與紙巾的人
that would register for lotion and tissues.
昨晚的派對真夠勁兒
That was some party last night, huh?
肯定挺瘋狂  我在這兒醒過來的
Yeah, it must have been. I woke up out here.
我非常確定我穿的是珍妮的內褲
And I'm pretty sure I'm wearing Jenny's underwear.
是啊
Yeah.
昨晚的事都記不太清了
The whole evening's a little fuzzy for me, too.
我只記得你
The last thing I remember is
喝邁克爾·波頓身上的酒
you doing body shots off of Michael Bolton.
我們所有人都喝邁克爾·波頓身上的酒了
All of us did body shots off of Michael Bolton.
連我們的媽媽們都能和諧共處
Even our moms got along.
開始我也不確定倆人能合得來
I wasn't sure they'd click at first, but...
但最后她們相處的還真和諧
in the end, they came together.
* 當一個男人愛上兩個女人 *
* When a man loves two women... *